HAYLEE DAMRON

Goleta, CA 93117 | 559-901-4573 | haylee@ucsb.edu

SUMMARY

High-performing operations manager with over 3 years of experience delivering successful improvements for business operations, profitability and team development. Resourceful project manager and compliance specialist with ability to thrive in fast-paced and changing environments. Dedicated to sustaining operational accuracy and delivering results for optimal profitability.

SKILLS

- Team Building/Leadership
- Business and Operations Management
- Staff training
- Staff development

EXPERIENCE

07/2020 to 06/2021

Operations Manager

Starbucks - Goleta, CA

- Managed company operations with responsibility for profit and loss, scheduling, training and inventory control.
- Collaborated with staff to maximize customer satisfaction, streamline procedures and improve bottom-line profitability.
- Implemented process improvements based on identification of productivity or quality issues.
- Trained, mentored and supported high-performing team, providing regular performance review, feedback and coaching in deficient areas.

09/2019 to Current

Student Employee

De La Guerra Dining Commons — Goleta, CA

- Covered front desk to greet visitors and field basic inquiries.
- Stocked materials in organized and useful manner.
- Assisted with different events during fall and winter quarters.
- Kept dishware, glasses and utensils ready for all customer needs by quickly scraping, washing and restacking items.
- Prepared food for service based on daily specials and chef's needs.

05/2018 to 08/2019

Assistant Manager

Cal Apparel – Visalia, CA

- Reviewed sales reports to enhance sales performance and improve inventory management accuracy.
- Maintained inventory accuracy by counting stock-on-hand and reconciling discrepancies.
- Optimized website, email campaigns and social media channels.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Expected in 06/2023 Bachelor of Arts: Geography With An Emphasis On GIS

University Of California, Santa Barbara — Santa Barbara, CA

06/2019 High School Diploma

Golden West High School - Visalia, CA

CERTIFICATIONS

• Barista Training - 2020

• Certified Barista Trainer, Starbucks - 2020

• Operations Management, Starbucks - 2021

REFERENCES

Connor Boggio: 805-297-0839 Patt Lundsky: 805-893-8459